Addicted to one-night stands or dependent on one another?
Love & Other Drugs is a drama, comedy, romance film directed by Edward Zwick.
Maggie is an alluring free spirit who won't let
anyone – or anything – tie her down.
But she meets her match in Jamie, whose relentless and nearly infallible charm serves
him well with the ladies and the cutthroat world of pharmaceutical sales.
Maggie and Jamie's evolving relationship takes them both by surprise, as they
find themselves under the influence of the ultimate drug: love.
Jamie Randall, played by Jake Gyllenhaal.
Maggie Murdock, played by Anne Hathaway.
Bruce Winston, played by Oliver Platt.
Dr. Stan Knight, played by Hank Azaria.
Josh Randall, played by Josh Gad.
Trey Hannigan, played by Gabriel Macht.
Love & Other Drugs is a 2010 American romantic comedy drama film directed, produced and co-written by Edward Zwick
and based on Jamie Reidy's 2005 non-fiction book Hard Sell: The Evolution of a Viagra Salesman.
Starring Jake Gyllenhaal, Anne Hathaway, Oliver Platt, Hank Azaria, Josh Gad and Gabriel Macht, the film tells the story of a
medicine peddler in 1990s Pittsburgh who starts a relationship with a young woman suffering from Parkinson's disease.
Love & Other Drugs premiered at the AFI Fest on November 4, 2010 and was
released in theaters on November 24, 2010, by 20th Century Fox.
It grossed $105 million against a $30 million budget,
and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of letter, sexual freedom, love, viagra, free spirit.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.